hotelworldasia.com 2012-12-26

# Privacy Policy | Questex Asia

We take individual privacy seriously. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at our websities. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using Questex websites, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. This Statement explains our policies and practices.

  * to implement computer, physical and procedural safeguards to protect the security and confidentiality of the personal data we collect
  * to limit the personal data collected to the minimum required to provide a better service
  * to permit only properly trained, authorized employees to access personal data 

These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit questex websites to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

## Information Collection

In order to provide a better service to you, we may collect information when you register with us, use our services, attend our functions, or communicate with us. 

We collect information and maintain a database about Hong Kong and overseas companies. In the process, we also collect personal information about individual contact persons of the companies or their employees (referrals).

If specific information is requested but not supplied, we may be unable to provide the requested service. We only retain personal data for so long as it is necessary.

Questex websites sometimes may offer content (e.g., contests, promotions) that is sponsored by or cobranded with identified third parties. By virtue of these relationships, the third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that you voluntarily submit to participate in the site activity. QUESTEX has no control over these third parties' use of this information.

## Use of your Personal Information

We give you choices and control over the collection and use of your Personal Information. You can update your Personal Information or remove your email address from our email list.

There are known methods that spammers can use to hide their identity by using other people's email address to send out emails. If you have any question about the genuineness of an email you receive that appears to be from QUESTEX, contact us at [webmaster@questexasia.com](mailto:webmaster@questexasia.com) and do not furnish personal information in response to that email.

We may conduct direct marketing via email, direct mail, telephone and other means of communication, or send e-newsletters to you. You may choose not to receive promotional materials, by simply telling us, and we will cease to do so, without charge.

## Cookie Technology

Cookies are commonly used to facilitate transmission and to provide more useful features. It is a piece of data stored in your computer. We use these devices to find out more about the use of our websites and user preferences, in order to improve our services. We may share summarized traffic data with advertisers. We note traffic, pages visited and time spent. You are not identified. Iif you agree by registering with us, we may link the information to you, you will receive information more suited to your interests.

You may set your browser to reject cookies, or tell you when a cookie is being sent.

Cookies are necessary for some features of the website to work, e.g., to maintain continuity during a session. If they are not accepted, those features may not work properly.

## Disclosure

We will keep the personal data we hold confidential but may provide information to personnel, agents, advisers, auditors, contractors, financial institutions, and service providers in connection with our operations or services ; our overseas offices, affiliates, business partners and counterparts ; persons under a duty of confidentiality to us ; persons to whom we are required to make disclosure under applicable laws in or outside Hong Kong; actual or proposed transferees or participants of our services.

## Commitment to Data Security

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.

## Copyright notice, disclaimer

Questex Asia Ltd. (Questex websites) is an Information Technology-related service which has been created to be easily accessible to all users, but it has limitations and risks which must be made known to the users before participating. By using the Service Users are consenting and agreeing to abide by these terms. QUESTEX will not be held liable for any losses, damages, costs or expenses arising from user's reliance on the accuracy of the content supplied /provided on questex websites. QUESTEX reserves the right to change, cancel or introduce new terms and conditions in the Agreement in its discretion at any time, and without prior notice.

## Privacy Contact Information

If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:

By mail:  
Questex Asia Ltd.  
13/ F., 88 Hing Fat Street, Causeway Bay, Hong Kong

By email:
